Basic Requirements
User Story: As a user I want to be able to guess the outcome of a random coin flip(heads/tails).
User Story: As a user I want to clearly see the result of the coin flip.
User Story: As a user I want to clearly see whether or not I guessed correctly.
Additional Challenges
Intermediate Challenge

User Story: As a user I want to clearly see the updated guess history (correct count/total count).
User Story: As a user I want to be able to quit the game or go again after each cycle.
Advanced Challenge

Let’s see if we can expand upon this challenge - what if instead of 2 options, there were 6?

User Story: As a user I want to be able to guess the outcome of a 6-sided dice roll (1-6), with the same feature set as the coin flip (see above).

You can add this directly to the existing program you’ve already written! As an additional challenge see if you can build the program such that the the user can choose between the two guessing games at startup, and possibly even switch after each cycle.

Pseudocoding project:

1. Welcoming screen
	- welcome text: "Guess coin flip heads or tails?"
	- input guess [1] heads or [2] tails

2. Random function
	- run random result == heads or tails
	- check whether guess == result
	- if True: print "guessed right"
	- if False: print "better luck next time"

3. History
	- to see updated guess history
	- set up counter to follow correct count/total count

4. Quit game or go again
	- set up option to continue or quit after each cycle
	- take into consideration with counter

